Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Royal Knights is an elite team of warriors chosen from only the most capable magic knights in all of the Clover Kingdom.
And the selection exam was finally underway.
Asta, Mimosa Vermillion, and the mysterious mage who called himself Zerx Lubner were among the first to battle in the tournament.
For some reason, Zerx made no attempt to fight.
So Asta and Mimosa were forced to charge into enemy territory on their own.
Do it now!
Just as victory was starting to look impossible, Zerx's trap spell was activated, bringing about a surprising comeback for Asta's team.
As for the contenders in the second battle...
My, what an eyesore!
I'll thank you not to interfere with the splendor of the magnificent Pierce Vermillion!
You waa!
Absolutely.
Let'sードディク are the actual items
D&W
Using the seat I covered the sand
assessment if you want to
Lead I
After you start my astrologues
I find my story
Every day
A year old, I chapter,
We walked all the stairs on the road
I can't see anything, but it's better when Iом
Oh, woe is me. Why must this wretched world be overrun with such aesthetically unpleasing creatures?
And why was I cursed to be born so beautiful amongst this pile of ugliness? Tragic.
I don't get this guy!
Please shut up! It's bad enough to think you're better than everybody else. Just keep it to yourself.
Uh-huh. Please don't fret, my homely friend.
What?
I understand that you envy my dashing good looks as anyone would.
But it isn't your fault that you're ugly.
You can't just go calling people ugly, you pretty boy, and I'm not ugly! Are you crazy?
No one in the world is as beautiful as Shore is! You're just a nasty, narcissistic, disgusting man!
Oh my! Such lowly words must never pass through the lips of a maiden.
What a shame. You almost have the potential to be pretty.
Feel free to use yours truly as an example.
He does know they're supposed to be teammates, right?
Mimosa! It's good to see you!
Have you come to gaze upon my glorious face?
Be careful not to get sick from an overdose of beauty.
Thanks for your concern.
But you're making me feel sick for a different reason.
How can you say such words?
Can you not comprehend my splendor?
Are you ill?
Allow me to heal you.
You're the one who's ill, big brother. If I'm being honest, I hope you lose this battle.
Come now. You shouldn't make jokes. You've never been very good at it.
Really?
Yes. Jokes are to be told with elegance and grace. In other words, they should be beautiful like you're truly...
Mimosa's older brother sure is unique. Not sure if that's a good thing or not.
It seems like she's having a hard time dealing with him, though.
Oh, hey! It's nice to meet you!
Mimosa's been a big help.
And you must be that commoner boy, Asta.
That's me!
Don't you dare speak to me so casually, you speck of dirt.
Whoa! His eyes just went dead!
I can't bear the sight of you.
Your aura is far from beautiful.
Your presence unsightly.
Clothes dirty.
And those muscles are grotesque.
The human form is designed to be beautiful exactly as it is, you idiot.
There's no need to train it. Such a thing is for the weak.
Well, yeah, I was pretty wimpy a long time ago.
It's hard not to be when you don't have any magic power.
That's why I worked so hard.
My muscles may be ugly, but they're my weapons.
We're born with a predetermined capacity for magic power, and that's that.
No matter what ugliness we stoop to in our struggle to change it, we can never do so.
Predetermined? I don't...
Your brains are as repulsive as your face.
How did a disgraceful commoner such as you even come to be a magic knight?
Good luck, Kirsch. I do want you to win this battle after all.
Mimosa! What a sweet sentiment!
Does this mean you've recognized my gorgeousness at last?
No, I'm just looking forward to the chance for me and Asta to obliterate you beyond recognition.
Do your best!
Obliterate!
It's such a beautiful choice of words!
That guy is flashy.
Even from here he's blinding me.
Yeah, he's a little much.
His name's Kirsch Vermillion, Mimosa's older brother.
Every bit as creepy as he is annoying.
That's no way to introduce him.
That man's the vice-captain of the Coral Peacocks.
Show some respect.
Despite the way he looks, I hear he essentially runs the squad by himself these days.
Since their captain, Dorothy Unsworth, is perpetually napping.
You said despite the way he looks.
That means you think he's a fashion disaster too, right, Spex?
Yeah, Spex agrees with us.
Glad you're with us, Spex.
That's not what I think.
Well, a little.
How much longer must I wait?
Bring on the next match.
I'm so restless I can't bear it.
Then let's begin.
For the next fight.
Team C, Kirsch, Sol, and Magna.
Versus Team D, Cesc, Adrian, and Willy.
Round one, match two.
Go!
Whoa!
Prepare to be overwhelmed by my magnificent visit.
Shut your trap!
We should get back to the waiting area so we can cheer for Magna's team.
Oh gosh, Asta's so close to me right now.
Someone's cocky.
You do realize that the next team they're going to be up against if they win is us, right?
Zerx.
Huh?
That stuff you were saying after the match.
About how you're not here to win, but you have a purpose in mind?
I said I was lying.
Come on, no more secrets.
You may get on my nerves, but we're still fighting on the same team.
And you're strong.
If all three of us work together, I know we have what it takes to win this tournament.
Asta.
Fine, I'll let you be the decoy again.
No, that's not what I meant when I said working together.
They're starting.
Have some of it, buddy!
Flame creation magic!
Grand slam!
You guys want some more?
Good, because here it comes.
I'm going to march straight over there, smash the crystal into smithereens, and take home the win.
How's that for a strategy?
That's it?
Now you're talking?
That's some impressive magic ability.
A junior-ranked fifth-class knight.
A peasant like him has no business being that brazen.
He's certainly off the list.
Okay, copper magic.
Pursuing jackals.
Bat dog, get back!
Let's see how you like this.
Hey!
Come over here and fight me yourself, you coward!
Come on!
My magic will burn you to a crisp and your little dogs, too!
Mowing everything down so indiscriminately.
You've no style to speak of.
Where the hell did you come from?
You're trying too hard at this.
There's no reason to act haphazardly when you have proficiency in both short and long-range spells.
The mana weeps for you.
What did you say?
Get a stronger read on your opponent's magic, almost surrendering to it.
Then you can launch the right attack for the distance.
If you can master that, your flame will burn much more beautifully.
Uh...
Different spells for different ranges, huh?
Okay.
So I just gotta stop trying too hard and surrender to their mana.
Fire!
First, the close-up ones.
And now for the ringleader in the pack.
Catch ya!
How's that?
Wait, where'd that little show-off go now?
Earth creation magic!
Raging Mother Goddess!
Out of my way!
I'm doing my part to make the Blue Rose Knights get a higher rank so Char will be happy!
Mud-Hinding Magic Flash Bomb!
Sorry, Miss, but I'm afraid it won't be that easy!
My bottomless mud will swallow up you and your golem!
How'd he get there?
Ah, crap!
Such a simple method of attack is an affront to my eyes!
What?
Your creation spell generates golems that can follow orders, yes?
Our strategy does not involve distracting our foe with this garish thing's wasteful size.
You watch your mouth!
Why not break it up into five smaller golems to cause them confusion?
An ambush from underground is also an attractive option.
Your creative mana should be capable of that.
Uh, sure.
Okay, Earth creation magic!
Multi-mother!
Goddess!
Oh!
Less power, more speed!
Your mud will never catch up with him now!
This isn't fair!
I'm outnumbered!
And since I've been guarding the crystal, it remains untouched and flawlessly beautiful!
Blossom to your heart's content!
Actually, you left your crystal wide open!
Water creation magic!
Priming Xealikens!
It's mine!
So sorry.
Oh my god!
It's too late for you.
My dazzling spell has you in its clutches.
Cherry blossom magic!
Raging magic cherry blossom storm of petals!
Bless my beautiful illusion!
Oh!
He's covered the field with a storm of cherry blossom petals?
Dammit!
I can't keep track of them in this!
All right!
This I can work with!
He just gave us a clear path to their crystal!
Go on!
Let's tread the flowered path to victory!
Burst into bloom!
Bloom!
Team Xe wins!
Whoa!
What a gorgeous display!
In this world, there are but two great cries.
Failing to radiate beauty in every way.
And failing to notice beauty.
All right!
We got through it somehow!
He's a pain, but I'm still glad he's here!
So fast!
There's a lot more to that guy than I thought there was!
Still creepy, though.
How the heck are we supposed to beat him when we get to the second round?
You know, perhaps the greatest crime is my unbridled handsomeness.
Tell me the truth.
What did you think of our battle?
Egregiously beautiful, yes?
That's right.
Of course.
Ha ha.
Why did I go along with that?
I'm so ashamed!
That flower spell.
The initial phase of it allowed him to create copies of himself to confuse the enemy.
Then, a storm of petals scattered across the field, obscuring their vision and scrambling their magic detection.
Once that was done, it gave his team a path to the crystal.
A feat like that could only be possible with the enormous magic power possessed by royalty.
Oh dear.
I'm so beautiful, it scares me.
Now I understand why Kirsch Vermillion is the most likely candidate to succeed Dorothy Unsworth as captain of the Coral Peacocks.
He's still weird, though.
Well...
Did you see that?
Your brother was incredible out there!
You two are obviously siblings!
I wish you wouldn't say that.
Silence, filth.
Your shrieking pollutes the air.
Now it's your turn to face me.
Too bad you're a cracked vessel that can't hold a drop of power.
My lovely spells will smash you to pieces.
Oh yeah?
Well I'm not worried, cause I've used a lot of bowls with cracked cinnamon, they can still hold stuff, even if it spills a little.
That's fine.
Oh, you've used a lot of cracked bowls.
Must be because you were so poor.
How unsightly.
No wait, that's not the point!
Sister Lily bought that bowl for us to eat out of!
Even though it's got cracks in it, it's the symbol of the love that she and I share, and it means the whole world to me!
And I'm gonna use it forever!
You just try and stop me!
Calm down, it was just a metaphor.
Your brains really are useless.
No!
Now it's time to begin the third match of the first round!
Team E, Finral, Leopold, and Hammond, versus Team F, Borja, Kyle, and Gaston!
I can't wait to heat up my flame magic so that our team can smoke out the competition!
And attacking them with my glass magic is sure to add a touch of grace and sophistication!
Watching the way Kirsch conducted himself in that last battle gave me a real spark of inspiration!
Why don't we try to fight beautifully as well?
I don't give a crap about being beautiful!
Forget your spark of inspiration, I'm bringing a full-blown inferno!
Besides, that guy kinda creeps me out!
No!
You should leave our attack strategy to me!
My magic will help us move swiftly!
We should make use of it!
I haven't fought alongside the Black Bulls all this time for nothing!
There's no way I'm gonna lose now!
Hot damn!
You're raring to go, huh?
I like that!
I'm sure you'll bring out the best in us!
Ha!
Leopold and Hammond are skilled fighters.
Go after the Black Bull!
I think I'm gonna let that happen!
He's right!
That spatial magic's pretty handy!
Borja!
Feather magic!
Feather tornado!
It's over for you!
Ready for this, Leopold?
Yep!
You're mine!
They've been trying to cause friendly fire all along!
And on top of that, I have a serious weakness to flame magic!
That portal user has a good eye for what works on this battlefield!
He assesses the area and drops us in the spot where our spells are most advantageous!
Glass creation magic!
To think the Black Bulls had an ace like him up their sleeve!
Why did they keep him under wraps for so long?
Now's my chance to attack with all the power I've got!
Flame magic!
Spiral flame!
Crystal destroyed!
Team E wins!
Got it!
I'm glad we won, but that was nerve-wracking!
Finally!
Now a delicious meal!
There's nothing like it!
And it'll bring us closer together!
A meal, huh?
Okay!
I say we make it a competition to see who can eat more!
Count me in, pal!
I don't think my stomach can take that right now!
Woo!
Wow, Fenroll!
You were awesome out there!
That was... great!
That spatial magic guy's a force to be reckoned with!
And he's just a junior knight?
Yeah, all the Black Bulls taking this exam are juniors!
I guess I underestimated them!
Because they're strong for the level of experience they have!
Their squad must have really stepped up this year!
Not bad for the one who brought shame upon the house of VOD!
But I'm about to show everyone how different we are!
It's time to continue on to the fourth battle of the first round!
Team G, Longris, Fragile, and Seke versus Team H, Gareth, Simon, and Medeo!
No, no, no!
This is all wrong!
Everyone here is so much stronger than me!
I should have known I was still too green to take this exam!
But Captain Jack said he wants to give the small fry a chance,
so it's kind of his fault for pressuring me!
This is a huge problem!
How did I get picked for this?
I mean, I volunteered, but still!
I can't be held responsible if I fail, right?
Are you okay there?
All the knights from the Black Bulls are junior level,
but they've been really successful!
I'm sure you're just as good as they are!
You've seen right through me!
What to do?
I hate to show off, but you leave me no choice!
I think I'll start by making a grand and glorious entrance on my Seke-shooting star!
That sounds like an excellent plan!
Our team's crystal is now completely covered with a barrier spell!
Good luck!
It's almost impossible to destroy!
I prefer to charge toward them at full speed!
Ha-ha!
Not a problem!
They're headed this way!
What kind of absurd vehicle is that?
Imbeciles!
We've set trap spells all over the ground!
You'll never make it pass!
KEY說
Thank you!
Stuff
Come on!
No!
No wait!
Well now...
He sliced through space!
How is that possible?
Crystal destroyed! Team G wins!
I hope you all witnessed my awesome triumph!
I'm Sake, Master of the Wind!
A beautiful victory for the illustrious House of Vod.
Wow, Finral's older brother really knows how to win a battle.
I hope my sword can cut through that kind of magic.
It's too bad that you'll never be anything more than a means of transport, but my magic is useful.
So do try to stay out of my portals during the next battle.
It would be a shame if you were to permanently disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would do to mother and father, I think a certain someone would be quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I want to prevent that, then I'll just have to win.
That's my dear brother.
Still insolent as ever.
loop getting it.
Yeah, I know where I can go.
Nice girl!
I know!
structure is putting me in the way back.
It's like crise to enter the museum.
I like looking into there
I know people who don't find theWasга
like running the движello so often,
I personally care.
And then I feel like I am suffering.
It feels like this is the money I want.
I know you.
I don't have a chance to citizenship wherever I am.
I'll make it true, my song, my days
この世界に響かせゆこう
駆け抜けた日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
流りくなった道さの暗には
輝ける明日を映すメロディ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I can see it
It's amazing how you can look at the whole battlefield at once
So you always know the best places to put your portals
Well I'm lucky to get personal training from Captain Yami every day
Really? What kind of training do you do with him?
For example, after we eat
if he's patting his belly like that it can mean only one thing you must need to use the bathroom
i'd know that angry knock anywhere that's the signal you're out of toilet paper
then there's newspaper time your bath time coffee milk
i'll give you the usual a rugged look that says i didn't shave but i did not shave
and that's pretty much it wow cool kind of sounds like the captain's using him
greetings peasants i've come to beautifully grace you with my beautiful beauty on this beautiful day
please try to contain your joy beautiful black clover even more beautiful page 76 mage x
my great beauty is beyond limits